# AARON JOHNSON

#### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



347.786.0266



aaron@ajfs.me



www.ajfs.me



Greater NYC Area

#### ABOUT ME

A multi-disciplinary pixel-perefectionist with a love for clean code, I bring a wealth of diverse experience to the table enabling me to hit the ground running on entry. I particularly excel in high-stakes environments where my contributions are essential toward both team and org KPIs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## INTERACTIVE DESIGNER POST STUDIOS 2019 - 2020

Using Photoshop, Illustrator & XD, I design mockups for digital interactive ad campaigns. Then, with HTML, CSS & JavaScript,
I craft the experiences for both web & mobile.

#### CREATIVE MANAGER

**TREMOR VIDEO** 2014 - 2018

Oversaw the distribution of pre-production mockups & post-production campaigns to various members of the design team and offered design guidance as needed. Worked collaboratively with sales and ad ops depts. in educating clientele as to our product offering and platform capabilities. Additionally, supplied support for maximum transparency surrounding campaign goals and outcomes.

#### DESIGNER

**TREMOR VIDEO** 2013 - 2014

Designed and built custom advertising experiences using Photoshop, ActionScript & JavaScript. Handled all levels of development, from animation to interaction to custom reporting exposure.

#### **EDUCATION**

## A.S., DIGITAL MEDIA COMMUNICATIONS KATHARINE GIBBS SCHOOL

2004 - 2006

Web major, focusing on design theory and and application through practical development. Acquired knowledge of Adobe CS, HTML, CSS & ActionScript. Graduated in the top 10 percentile.

### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Lambda School

2019 - 2020

Continuing web development education, focusing on current technologies and best practices. Technologies include React.js for frontend development, Node.js (backend), Python (CS theory, data structures & algorithms) as well as Knex & PostgreSQL for query-building and database management.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML	
css	_
JAVASCRIPT	
REACT	
NODE	
PYTHON	
POSTGRES	
GIT	

#### **HOBBIES**



Gaming

#### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.



Coding

Fitness

ss Reading